When using a text box, press Enter to apply changes, Ctrl+Enter to wrap, and Esc or click another area to cancel typing.
When a skin is locked by your settings, hold down Ctrl and right-click to see the general context menu.
To batch drag, hold Ctrl+Alt to select skins and drag.
Middle-press a skin to toggle its style/size (if available).
Some skins have exclusive settings and other styles/sizes.
If the skin shows abnormality, please try to refresh it.
If the skin with the web feed stops working, try restarting Rainmeter.
By deactivating some skins, you can optimize the performance of your computer.
Please make sure that your Rainmeter is up to date.
You can find detailed solutions in the Help Center.
0% EASTER EGGS